1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-create-new-account"))
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), "salahemailgmail.com")
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "")
25. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "")
29. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-Email"), "Please enter a valid email address")
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-required"), "Required")
41. takeScreenshot()
45. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), "agung.priyadi@gtech.digital")
49. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
53. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Las")
57. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
61. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Registration/verify-length"), "Password length is 6-20 digits")
65. takeScreenshot()
69. closeBrowser()